Jamie Joseph Heiney

Bookkeeper

About Me

Experienced accountant specialized in bookkeeping tasks that include accounts payables and receivables, processing invoices, making credit card payments, and taking care of the banking. I have a strong knowledge of QuickBooks, Google Sheets, and Excel and have experience designing and implementing comprehensive loan tracking systems using different software.

Skills

- · Bank & Credit Card Reconciliation
- Excel Cash Flow Management
- Simplification of Complex Topics
- QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online)
- Budgeting and Financial Planning
- Google Sheets
- Excellent Communication

Experience

Accountant at Alpha Capital LLC

Dec 2019 - May 2022

- · Managed all bookkeeping needs for several capital funding companies
- Created chart of accounts, bank reconciliation, and organized, formatted, and imported large amounts of data from CRMS, software, and Google Sheets
- Designed and implemented a comprehensive loan tracking system using multiple interlinked Google Sheets and Google App Scripts that allowed owners, salespeople, and outside investors to view and update vital information
- Utilized the accounting system for multiple companies owned by Alpha Capital and provided consulting services to other companies

Nursing Home Game Creator at Games 4 Life

Feb 2017 - Feb 2019

- · Developed interactive group games for elderly care facilities to address the lack of stimulating and engaging content for elders
- Grew client base to over 30 nursing homes and hundreds of happy users
- · Managed accounts receivable and gained a broad understanding of business and management

AP Regional Manager at Beyond Healthcare LLC

Jan 2015 - Mar 2017

- · Oversaw AP transactions and personnel for four nursing homes
- Negotiated with vendors for more favorable contracts
- · Maintained all accounts payable reports, spreadsheets, and files
- · Acted as a liaison between corporate and nursing home accounts payable departments
- Managed emails and website domains for the corporate staff

Education

Certificate in Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping QuickBooks

Online Essential Training QuickBooks Pro Essential Training Yeshiva Toras Chaim High School

Took an accounting course, Accounting Coach course by Harold Averkamp, and tested and received a certificate. Also studied at Yeshiva Toras Chaim High School, obtaining a diploma with a 3.4 GPA.

Contact: 305-801-7497